Contact info

Email

mollofernando374@gmail.com

Address

Cochabamba - Bolivia

Phone

(+591) 60750774

Skills

Manual Testing

Functional Testing
Non-Functional Testing
Black and Gray Box Testing
Cross Browser Testing
API Testing
E2E Testing
ISTQB Knowledge
TDD

Scrum - Agile

Manage Testing

Jira – Confluence

TestRail

Test Link

Windows (Server) – Linux

Automation Testing

Jenkins – Cl

Postman - SoapUI

BrowserStack

Cypress

Selenium Webdriver

JMeter

Git – GitHub

Appium – Mobile Testing

AWS, Azure, Azure DevOps

Docker – Kubernetes

Databases

SQL Server MySQL - PostgreSQL MongoDB

Programming

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Java – JUnit Python – Pytest C# – .NET Knowledge

FERNANDO MOLLO

Quality Assurance Engineer

Profile

QA Engineer with more than Five years of experience working in IT, creating mostly SaaS or Web Applications for companies in industries such as Software, and Insurance, combining strong analytical and technical skills with a problem-solving mindset. I am passionate about agility, and innovation so I help teams and QAs enhance their practices to deliver high-value solutions to their customers.

Experience

QA Engineer – (05/2021 to Today)

Company: "NICE IN-CONTACT", Cochabamba – Bolivia

- Manual testing checking functionality, interface, and compatibility.
- Smoke, Sanity, Regression, APIs, and End to End testing for Contact Center.
- Automation Testing with Cypress, JavaScript, Jenkins, AWS, Git, and Postman.

Software Quality Assurance Engineer Automation– (03/2020 to 04/2021)

Company: "JALASOFT", Cochabamba - Bolivia

- Functional testing according to the requirements and standards.
- Analyze, design, and execute test cases, test suites, and test plans.
- Automation Testing using Selenium, Python, Java, Git, Azure, Azure DevOps.

QA Analyst- (01/2019 to 03/2020)

Company: "C_SPACE", Cochabamba - Bolivia, Job-like Contactor

- Manual and E2E testing, API Testing with Postman on the CRM App.
- Cross Browser, Blackbox, Gray Box, and Functional Testing.
- Performance, Load, and Stress testing with JMeter.

Software Quality Assurance Tester – (01/2018 to 12/2018)

Company: "UNIVIDA S.A.", Cochabamba – Bolivia

- Manual, UI, and Functional Testing on the Mobile Application "UNIVidaApp"
- Tests on emulators, and mobile Android devices, and defect reports.
- Test Plan, test cases, user manual, reports, and Dashboards in Confluence.

Education

- Bachelor's degree: Systems Engineer (2011 to 2018)
 "Universidad Mayor de San Simon", Cochabamba Bolivia
- Manual Testing Training: **Scholar** (05/2019 to 01/2020)

"Jala University", Cochabamba - Bolivia

• Student – (01/2018 to 12/2018)

"CBA (Centro Boliviano Americano)", Cochabamba - Bolivia

Languages

- English Level B2: Reading (Good), Listening (Intermediate), Speaking (Good)
- Spanish (Native Language)

Certifications

• They are on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/fernando-mollo/